yeezysupply.com 2019-06-07

# YEEZY PRIVACY | YEEZY SUPPLY

**Privacy Policy**

**Protecting your Privacy**

Yeezy Apparel LLC ("Company" or "we", "us", or "our") is strongly committed to protecting the privacy of your personal information collected at or in connection with an our website. This Online Privacy Policy (the “Policy”) applies to those websites that display or link to this Policy. This Policy applies to data collected by us through our Website and services that display these terms. It does not apply to those sites, services and products that do not display or link to this Policy or that have their own privacy policies. This Policy describes the information we collect and how we use it. By visiting our Website, you are accepting the practices described in this Policy. If you do not agree to the terms of this Policy, please do not use the Website.

**Consent to Collection and Processing**

This Website may be operated, in whole or in part, from a country other than the United States. By using our Website, you consent to having your personal information transferred to and processed in a jurisdiction outside of the United States.

**What Information about me does yeezysupply.com collect and store?**

Our privacy policy is simple: Except as disclosed below, we don't sell, trade, give away, or rent your personal information to any company, other than our partner, adidas, which operates this Website. One of the basic principles we've tried to follow in designing this Website is to limit the information we collect from and share about you. 

**Personal Information**

We collect and store information that you provide to our Website or our Customer Service Department or that we receive from third parties (such as companies providing commercially available databases). For example, when you place an order, we collect and store some or all of the following information that you provide: name, billing address, shipping address, email address, telephone number, and credit card number and expiration date. We collect your e-mail addresses and zip code if you subscribe to our newsletter and we collect your mobile number if you opt in to receive text messages. You may unsubscribe at any time by following the instructions located within each newsletter or linked to each text message. We also collect and store your geolocation information. Registration may be required and personal information collected in certain areas of the Website in which you specifically and knowingly provide such information, e.g. community postings (i.e., chat or bulletin boards), suggestions, or customer service requests. When we run a contest or sweepstakes relating to our Website, it will be accompanied by a set of rules. The rules for each contest/sweepstakes will specify how the information gathered from you for entry will be used and disclosed, if it is different than as described in this Policy. Personal information will be collected only if you voluntarily submit it to our sponsors or us.

**Usage Information**

Through your use of our Website, we may also gather certain information about your use of our Website ("Usage Information"). Generally, this information is collected through "traffic data". We collect and store certain other information automatically whenever you interact with our Website. For example, we collect your IP address, browser information and reference site domain name every time you visit our Website. We also collect information regarding customer traffic patterns and site usage. This information is used to analyze and improve our Website, to provide our customers with a fulfilling shopping experience, and to personalize the Website, our communications with you, and your shopping experience.

**How does yeezysupply.com use cookies, advertising, and online tracking?**

Like many websites, we use "cookies", files stored on your computer's hard drive by your browser to identify account holders and to optimize their shopping experience. Cookies also allow us to hold selections in a shopping cart when a user leaves this Website without checking out and send you reminder e-mail about your shopping orders and other shopping opportunities. Most browsers accept cookies automatically but allow you to disable them. We recommend that you leave cookies "turned on" so that we can offer you a better shopping experience. You may occasionally get cookies from companies advertising on our behalf to tailor advertisements shown to you for goods and services. We do not control these cookies, and these cookies are not subject to our Website. Our systems do not recognize browser “Do Not Track” signals, but several of our service providers who utilize these cookies and other tracking technologies on our Website enable you to opt out of this type of advertising. For more information about third party cookies, including information about how to opt out of these technologies, visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp> or [www.aboutads.info/choices/](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/).

We use Google Analytics and Google AdWords on the Website to collect Usage Information, to analyze how users use the Website and to provide advertisements to you on other websites.  For more information about how to opt out of having your information used by Google Analytics, visit <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/>.  You can learn more about advertising and online tracking and how to opt out of such practices in the paragraph above.

**Interest-Based Advertising**

We also use third party companies **,** including Google Analytics and Google Adwords, to measure and target ads on our behalf about products and services tailored to your interests. We allow these third-party companies to use cookies, web beacons, pixel tags and similar technologies to collect or receive information about your interaction with us on our Website and elsewhere on the internet (“Tracking Data”) and use such Tracking Data to display ads for us and other companies when you visit this or other websites. These third-party companies may not recognize browser “Do Not Track” signals. If you would like to opt out of the collection and use of Tracking Data for ad targeting, please visit [www.aboutads.info/choices/](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/).   **For more information about how to opt out of having your information used by Google Analytics, visit**[ **https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/**](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/) **.   **

**Is Information collected from children?**

We do not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from children under 13.

**How does yeezysupply.com use your personal information?**

We may use your personal information to provide the products and services that you have ordered or requested, to process and ship orders, to provide customer service, to provide other services to you, and to personalize the Website, our communications with you, and your shopping experience. Your information also may be used to contact you about sales, new products, new site features, special offers, and personalized offers based on your location, unless you have opted to not receive promotional communications. The information we collect may be combined with information obtained from other companies. We may also combine this information with other information we collect as you interact with us across apps, social media and marketing messages we send you. Aggregating data allows us to update and correct the information contained in our database and to provide you with product recommendations and special offers.

**How does yeezysupply.com share your personal Information?**

Company - Except as described in this Policy, we will not disclose your personal information outside of our Company and our partner, adidas, which operates this Website, without your consent. Our Partners - Our Websites may allow you to choose to share your personal information with select partners of ours so that they can contact you about their products, services or offers. Other sites do not share your contact information with third parties, but give you a choice as to whether you wish to receive communications from us on behalf of a business partners about its specific offer (without transferring your personal information to the third party). Co-Branded Sites - Some Company services may be co-branded by us and another company, with the privacy policy of both us and the other company displayed at the website. The information you provide, such as on registration forms, is collected by both us and the other company. Third-party Service Providers - We may hire other companies to provide services on our behalf, such as marketing, analytics, credit card processing, shipping, stocking orders, providing customer service, and fraud protection. These service providers have access only to such personal information needed to perform their functions and are contractually obligated to maintain the confidentiality and security of your information. They are restricted from using, selling, distributing or altering this data in any way other than to provide the requested services. Legal and Safety Disclosures - We may access or disclose information about you, including the content of your communications, in order to: (a) comply with the law or respond to lawful requests or legal process; (b) protect the rights or property of us or our customers, including the enforcement of our agreements or policies governing your use of our Websites and services; or (c) act on a good faith belief that such access or disclosure is necessary to protect the personal safety of our employees (and employees of our partners and service providers), customers or the public. Corporate Transactions - We may disclose personal information as part of a corporate transaction such as a merger or sale of assets.

**How does yeezysupply.com use usage information?**

We use Usage Information to help us determine how people use parts of the Website and who our readers are. This allows us to improve our Website and ensure that it is as appealing as we can make it for as many people as possible. We also use Usage Information to provide statistical "ratings" information in aggregated form to our partners and other third parties about how our users collectively use the Website.  We may combine Usage Information about you with other information, including Personal Information, about you in order to personalize the Website and our communications with you and to provide you with information likely to be of interest to you.

**What steps are taken to help secure personal information?**

Our goal is to deliver performance to you in every way. That includes security. Personal information collected at our Website is stored in secure operating environments that are not available to the public. Only those employees and service providers who need access to personal information in order to do their jobs are allowed access, each having confidentiality obligations. To protect the security of your information during transmission, we use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input. For example, when using a credit card to make an on-line purchase, your personal information is encrypted before you conduct your transaction. Most browsers will give a visual indication of when your connection is secure. For example, Internet Explorer will show a padlock icon in the lower right of the browser window. If you place an order through our Website, you will be asked to set up an account and provide an e-mail address and password. In order to help protect your personal information, you should be careful about providing your password to others. If you wish to cancel your account, or if you become aware of any loss, theft or unauthorized use of your password, please contact Customer Service. Please refer to the last section of this Policy (How to Contact Us) for more information. While we try our best to safeguard your personal information once we receive it, no transmission of data over the Internet or any other public network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure.

**What happens when I link to or from another website?**

Our Website may contain links to other websites. Our Policy does not apply to the practices of other websites and we are not responsible for the actions and privacy policies of third parties. We encourage you to be aware of when you leave our Website and to read the privacy policies of each website that you visit.

**Can yeezysupply.com use information I share in public areas, chat rooms and newsgroups?**

Please remember that any information you share in public areas, such as message boards or feedback sections, becomes public. Our Policy does not apply to any information you choose to make public. Please be careful about what you disclose and do not post any personal information that you expect to keep private.

**How do I opt-out of receiving promotions?**

To opt out of receiving our promotional communications, please contact [info@yeezysupply.com](mailto:info@yeezysupply.com)

**How do I contact you about privacy-related questions?**

If you have questions or comments about our privacy practices, please contact us by e-mail [info@yeezysupply.com](mailto:info@yeezysupply.com) or by mail at the following address

adidas America  
Attn: Legal Privacy Policy  
5055 N Greeley Ave  
Portland, OR 97217

**How does this policy apply to European Union and Swiss Residents?**

To offer our products and services, we may need to transfer your personal information outside the European Union and Switzerland.  If you choose to provide us with your information, you consent to the transfer and storage of that information on our servers located in the United States.   **We comply with applicable laws when transferring personal information outside the European Union and Switzerland.**  Any questions or concerns regarding the use or disclosure of your information should be directed to us through an email at [info@yeezysupply.com](mailto:info@yeezysupply.com) . We will investigate and attempt to resolve complaints and disputes regarding use and disclosure of your information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. For clarity, this "European Union and Swiss Residents" section of this Privacy Policy applies only to residents of the EU and Switzerland.

**What is the Secure Shopping Guarantee?**

We use the industry standard encryption protocol known as Secure Socket Layer (SSL) to keep your order information secure. We've established a Secure Shopping Guarantee for every transaction that you make with www.yeezysupply.com. Should any unauthorized charges appear on your credit card as a result of shopping with www.yeezysupply.com, you must notify your credit card provider in accordance with its reporting rules and procedures. If you have more questions regarding our policy, you can send us an e-mail at: [info@yeezysupply.com](mailto:info@yeezysupply.com).

**Applicable Law and Jurisdiction**

Oregon state law governs the interpretation of this Policy and applies to claims for breach of them regardless of conflict of laws principles. Both parties consent to exclusive jurisdiction and venue in courts sitting in Portland, Oregon. Both parties waive all defenses of lack of personal jurisdiction and forum non conveniens.

**Changes to This Online Privacy Policy**

We will update this Policy as needed to reflect changes in our services and customer feedback. When we post changes to this Policy, we will revise the "last updated" date at the bottom. If there are material changes to this Policy or in how we will use your personal information, we will notify you by prominently posting a notice of such changes prior to implementing the change. We encourage you to periodically review this Policy to remain informed of how we are protecting your information.

REV: April 1, 2019
